Chad McKinney

Payson UT 84651

(801) 615-9705 · cfmckinney@gmail.com

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Highly motivated, creative marketing and product manager exceeding expectations of customers and clients. Over four years of experience in fast-paced, rapid-growth environments. Motivated by bringing excitement, energy, and encouragement to team members.

Project Management ● Strong Verbal Communication

Written Communication ● Customer Support ● Positive ● Problem Solver

Focused ● Learner ● Leader ● Collaborative

EXPERIENCE

Skipio

Nov 2018 - Apr 2019

Implementations Specialist

American Fork, UT

- Managed relationships with customers participating in software beta programs to train customers and gather valuable feedback leading to product improvement
- Improved customer satisfaction through professional interactions and individualized problem resolution
- Created and improved integrations between Skipio and various additional software platforms to automate and simplify workflows

Red Pajardo, Inc

Aug 2016 - Aug 2018

Houston, TX

Operations and Brand Manager

- Developed, designed, and oversaw implementation of consistent branding material, logo, signage, and clinic design
- Developed profitability and performance metrics that established consistent measurability among multiple remote sites which resulted in profitability in an average of under 12 months
- Implemented and oversaw CRM and POS software solutions to increase repeat business, drive referrals, and create targeted marketing campaigns

Alta Sol

Apr 2016 – Aug 2016

Orem, UT

Canvassing Manager

- Analyzed local markets' solar demand and prospected based on electrical power providers' services and costs to maximize rates of success
- Presented current and potential customers with the benefits of alternative power then developed and presented personalized solar solutions to fit needs
- Enhanced employee development through team meetings and one-on-one coaching, helping to achieve potential and accomplish individual and team goals

INTERESTS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- Digital design
- Software development
- Eagle Scout Award Recipient with two additional silver palms
- Humanitarian Service Houston, Texas

SOFTWARE

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, SQL, Postgres
- Adobe CC (Photoshop, Illustrator, Audition, Premier Pro)
- Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Access, Word)

EDUCATION

Utah Valley University – Woodbury School of Business	July 2015	
Bachelor of Science, Business Management – Marketing Emphasis	Orem, UT	
DevMountain	Current	
Full-Stack Software Development	Lehi. UT	